Prescott S. Bush Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Photographs and Films, undated, 1955-1962
  - TV, WHNB, 1962 May
  - TV, WHCT, 1962 April
  - TV, WTIC, 1962 April
  - TV, NBC news, 1962
  - “Key to a Future”, 1962
- Series VII: Scrapbooks, 1952-1962
  [A portion of these scrapbooks have been disassembled and the clippings photocopied for preservation purposes.]
  - 1952 July 28 - December 12 (Box 1)
  - 1953 January 2 - December 20 (Box 2)
  - 1954 January 2 - December 26 (Box 3)
  - 1955 January 2 - December 29 (Box 4)
  - Floods, 1955 August 19 - October 18 (Box 5)
  - 1955-1956 December 31 - June 14 (Box 6)
  - 1956 June 19 - December 13 (Box 7)
  - 1957 January 2 - December 31 (Box 8)
  - 1958 January 3 - December 31 (Box 9)
  - 1959 January 2 - December 23 (Box 10)
  - 1960 January 5 - July 31 (Box 11)
  - 1960 August 4 - December 31 (Box 12)
  - 1961 January 1 - June 29 (Box 13)
  - 1961 July 1 - December 31 (Box 14)
  - 1962 January 4 - October 19 (Box 15)
  - 1962 January 2 - May 31 (Box 16)
  - undated (Box 16)